Guide to the Marilyn J. Boxer Papers SC1212
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Additional Papers, Accession ARCH-2016-092
  - R (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Rouamet. Gustavo (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Revue d'economie politique (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - S (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - T (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - V (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Villat - Lachuel (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - W (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Y (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Z (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Law (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Lesbianism (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Lib. Action (media) (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - linguistics lit (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Local Hx (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Lowell Mills (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Religion (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Medieval (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Rome (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - R (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Reu - Ref (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Revolutions (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Rousseau (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Articles 1970s (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Socialism (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Socialist Lx (yellow files), 1970s (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - S (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Sanger (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Scott (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Scott - gender (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Scott (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Scot and Tilly PCs essays (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Shorten (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - S Klar (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Roth/Sklar (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Smith notes (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Stats (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - World stats, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Mitcult Stats (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Stats - US (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Euro stats (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Steam Social history (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Steam lives of labor and others (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - St. Simonnianism (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Suffrage (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - T (Box 10, Folder 36)
- Additional Papers, Accession ARCH-2018-072
  - Pawlowski - Les Syndicats feminins …photocopy, 1912 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Vernieres - Camille Frison photocopy, 1908 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Kleek, Mary van - Artificial flower makers photocopy, 1913 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Outline: questions to raise (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - ILL - interlibrary loan requests (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - ILL - interlibrary loan requests (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Library (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Library: notes and ILL requests (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Notes and articles (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Journals [notes] (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Les fleuristes [notes], 1874-1875 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - La Fronde [notes] (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - R. R. R. [notes] (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Bodeve - La petite lotte photocopy, 1907 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Fashion (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Gagneur - La Calvaire des femmes photocopy, 1867 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Just deserts - UCR history Dept. newsletter (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Women's studies, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Women in history syllabi, 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Feminine flower makers - card index and slides (Box 1)
  - Periodicals, first paper, Flower Beings - articles [card index] (Box 2)
  - Flowermakers 1 - M (Box 2)
  - Card index, no label (Box 2)
  - Card index, no label (Box 2)
  - Femina [slides] (Box 2)
  - Femina slides 1-40 (Box 2)
  - Femina slides 41-80 (Box 2)
  - Femina slides 81-105 (Box 2)
  - Flowermakers lecture slides 1-38 (Box 2)
  - WCW - 2 (Box 2)
  - Images 19 C art - 2 (Box 2)
  - Slides (Box 2)
  - Women in History - WS 341B Prof. M.J. Boxer (Box 3)
  - Rebellious Women - WS 595 Boxer, 1983 Fall (Box 3)
  - Women in American History WS341A Boxer, 1983 Fall (Box 3)
  - Women's syllabi, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Women's syllabi, 1975 Jan 25 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - UN Mid-decade conference on women (1 of 2), 1980 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - UN Mid-decade conference on women (2 of 2), 1980 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - letter to MB from Johnna, 1980 Oct 24 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - papers by Mary Lou Emery (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Women's Work Week, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Women's Week workshop - teaching women's history, 1974 Apr (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Women's Week, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - National Women's Studies Assoc. Conference, 1984 Jun 24-28 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - PSR WSA Conference, Los Angeles, 1976 Oct (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - SP - WSA newsletter (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - PSW RWSA USC, 1978 May (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - IWY Conference USC, 1977 Jun (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Western Assoc. of Women Historians (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - West Coast Assoc. of Women Historians (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - National Organization for Women (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - CAL annual report, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - UC Riverside History schedule of classes, 1974 Winter (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Women's week student responses, 1975 Apr (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - NOW (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Women's Studies - misc. colleges and universities (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Liberated Woman's appointment calendar, 1971 (Box 3)
  - Liberated Woman's appointment calendar, 1975 (Box 3)
  - Liberated Woman's appointment calendar, 1976 (Box 3)
  - Liberated Woman's appointment calendar, 1977 (Box 3)
  - Woman's calendar for …, 1978 (Box 3)
  - Clippings summer 1975 forward (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Warhoop; Highlander [misc. issues] (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - UC Riverside Women's resource center [newsletter and ephemera] (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Bulletin board [ephemera] (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Birth control handbook - Montreal, 1969 Dec (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Highlander (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Warhoop (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Daily Aztec (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Longest Revolution (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Clippings (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - VD Handbook Montreal, 1972 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Women's studies publications (Box 4)
  - Women's studies pamphlets (Box 4)
  - San Diego State University - women's studies ephemera, 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - San Diego State University - women's studies ephemera (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - San Diego State University - women's studies catalogs, 1975 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Student Work
    Conditions Governing Access
    Student work is restricted for 75 years from date of creation.
    - Class records books, 1974-1984 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - San Bernardino Valley College - Women in History: student papers, 1971 Fall (Box 6, Folder 2)